<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SangGyu An</title>
    <link>https://bbeat2782.github.io/DataSciencePortfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SangGyu An</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bbeat2782.github.io/DataSciencePortfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Metacritic User Rating Prediction</title>
      <link>https://bbeat2782.github.io/DataSciencePortfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bbeat2782.github.io/DataSciencePortfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Why it matters? Oftentimes, you see a bad review of a movie from critics and think that you won&amp;rsquo;t enjoy the movie. However, when you go to a theater and watch the movie for yourself, you find out you actually enjoy the movie more than you thought. This happened to me when I watched Extraction 2, Transformers: Rise of the Beasts, and Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 3. The opposite situation also happened, and sometimes, critic ratings are similar to user ratings such as Fast X and John Wick 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: San Diego Collision EDA</title>
      <link>https://bbeat2782.github.io/DataSciencePortfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bbeat2782.github.io/DataSciencePortfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Why it matters? In Korea, car navigation systems notify drivers when they enter &amp;lsquo;accident-prone areas,&amp;rsquo; helping them stay alert and avoid potential accidents. However, similar services are not commonly available in navigation systems in the US. As a result, I became curious about identifying accident-prone areas in San Diego to raise awareness when I drive in the future.
Moreover, as an inexperienced driver, I have been told lane changes are the most challenging task when driving in Korea, partly due to narrow lanes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://bbeat2782.github.io/DataSciencePortfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bbeat2782.github.io/DataSciencePortfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello. I&amp;rsquo;m SangGyu An, who is passionate about learning and solving problems with data. With a major in Data Science at UC San Diego, I&amp;rsquo;m continuously seeking to expand my horizons and stay at the forefront of this rapidly evolving field.
As a firm believer in the power of data, I am dedicated to uncovering meaningful insights and translating them into actionable solutions. My portfolio showcases a collection of projects where I’ve harnessed data to tackle a variety of challenges, ranging from San Diego Collision EDA to MetaCritic User Rating prediction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://bbeat2782.github.io/DataSciencePortfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bbeat2782.github.io/DataSciencePortfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description> Platform URL LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sanggyu-an-704104126/ Github: https://github.com/bbeat2782 Medium: https://medium.com/@bbeat2782 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
